# Muhammad Isyraff Irfan

**Bachelor of Computer Science** (Computer Network and Security)

I am a Computer Science student in School of Computing, UTM that acquire a positive attitude and good at handling work management. Besides that, I am knowledgeable in user interface and also user experience. I am a good team player and have great problem solving skills that can be applied to resolve any problem that might arise as I aim for excellence. Therefore, I am an excellent fit for your organisation.





isyraff.irfan@gmail.com +60 143485052



## **EDUCATION**

Jan 2016 - Dec 2017 Sijil Pelajaran Malaysia (SPM), SM SAINS TUANKU MUNAWIR Achieved 4A+ 2A 1A- 2B+

Jul 2018 - Apr 2019 Foundation in Engineering, **UiTM Dengkil** Achieved CGPA 3.44

▶ Sept 2019 - Present **Bachelor of Computer Science** (Computer Network and Security), Universiti Teknologi Malaysia Current CGPA 3.76

## PAST PROJECT

▶ July 2021

## Internship Application system

- A website system universities student to apply internship and lecturer will either approve or reject the application.
- The website built using HTML and CSS for the front-end, and used MySQL for back-end
- ▶ Jan 2022

## **Facilities Tracker**

- · Built for Android system, users uses to navigate facilities such as mosque that uses Google Map API
- Developed using Android Studio and Firebase for the database

## LANGUAGE PROFICIENCY

Malay

● ● ● ● (Native Speaker)

Enalish

● ● ● ● (Proficient)

## REFERENCE

Dr Yusliza Yusoff (Academic Advisor)

+60 127092524

gyusliza@utm.my

# WORKING EXPERIENCE

▶ Aug 2020 - Aug 2021 Technical Assistant, UTM Charity Shop Work as a part timer to handle sales and prepares graphical material for promotional purposes.

▶ Sept 2020 - Aug 2021 Graphic Designer, Boss Gold Esport Work as a part timer to prepares graphical material to promote team branding

# **EXTRA CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES**

▶ Sept, 2 2020 - Nov, 5 2020 Editor Unit, 63rd UTM Convocation Ceremony Work as an editor that responsible for graduates

convocation pictures

May, 28 2021 - May, 29 2021 Head of Multimedia Unit, Cultural Festival 2021 Responsibled for leading multimedia unit in providing graphical material for promotional purposes and advertisement

Oct, 25 2021 - Dec, 18 2021 Head of Editor Unit, 64th UTM Convocation

Given the responsibility to lead the editing unit in terms of using Photoshop for graduate's pictures

Oct, 11 2021 - Sept, 18 2021 Head of Multimedia Unit, Kelab Fotokreatif (KFK) Responsibled for leading multimedia unit in providing graphical content to promote club's events on social media

## SKILLS

Web Development (HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, PHP)

● ● ● ● (Proficient)

Database Management (MySQL, Firebase)

● ● ● ● (Proficient)

Programming Language (Java, C++)

Moderate)

Prototyping (Invision, Adobe XD)

● ● ● ● (Proficient)

Graphic Design (Photoshop, Illustrator, Canva)

● ● ● ● (Advanced)

Video Editing (Adobe Premiere Pro, After Effect)

● ● ● ● (Proficient)